let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which of the following is used for comments in C++?",
    answer: "both // comment or /* comment */",
    options: [
      " /* comment */",
      "// comment */",
      " // comment",
      "both // comment or /* comment */"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the use of the indentation in c++? ",
    answer: "distinguishes between comments and code",
    options: [
      "r distinguishes between comments and inner data",
      "distinguishes between comments and outer data",
      "distinguishes between comments and code",
      "r distinguishes between comments and outer data",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is used to terminate the function declaration in C++?",
    answer: ";",
    options: [
      ";",
      "]",
      ")",
      ":",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "What is Inheritance in C++?",
    answer: "Deriving new classes from existing classes",
    options: [
      "Deriving new classes from existing classes",
      "Overloading of classes",
      "Classes with same names",
      "Wrapping of data into a single class",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "What is meant by a polymorphism in C++?",
      answer: "class having many forms",
      options: [
        "class having only single form",
        "class having four forms",
        "class having many forms",
        " class having two forms",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Pick the incorrect statement about inline functions in C++? ",
    answer: "They are generally very large and complicated function",
    options: [
      "They are generally very large and complicated function",
      "These functions are inserted/substituted at the point of call ",
      "They reduce function call overheads",
      "Saves overhead of a return call from a function",
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which of the following is used for generic programming?",
  answer: "Templates",
  options: [
    "Virtual functions",
    "Modules",
    "Templates",
    "Abstract Classes",
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "Which of the following is correct about templates?",
  answer: "All of the mentioned",
  options: [
    "It is a type of compile time polymorphism",
    "It allows the programmer to write one code for all data types",
    "Helps in generic programming",
    " All of the mentioned",
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Implicit return type of a class constructor is?",
  answer: "class type itself",
  options: [
    "not of class type itsel",
    "class type itself",
    "a destructor of class type",
    "a destructor not of class type",
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "How many types of linkages are there in C++?",
  answer: "3",
  options: [ 
    "1",
    "2",
    "3",
    "4",
  ]
  },
  
  ];